Guide to the Anthony Taussig collection of English legal manuscripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Taussig Catalog # 305: 17th and 18th cent. MS reports of King's Bench 1694-1701 said to have been taken by Peter King, c. 440 pp. [2001.3.24 V. Tunkel] (Box 40)
- Taussig Catalog # 306: F.W. Sanders, Uses and trusts, 4th ed., 1824 (printed), annotated [2001.4.11(a) J. Rees], 2 (Box 40)
- Taussig Catalog # 307: 17th cent. (24 Aug. 1694) MS autograph opinion of Henry Gould, 1 p. [2001.4.11(b) J. Rees] (Box 40)
- Taussig Catalog # 308: 19th cent. (1801) MS statements re: murder of William Bailey, 20 pp. [2001.5.1(a) A.R. Heath] (Box 40)
- Taussig Catalog # 309: 19th cent. MS notebook of Francis Hobler, an attorney, 40 ff. [2001.5.29 Pendlebury Books] (Box 40)
- Taussig Catalog # 310.1-310.4: 16th cent. (mostly last quarter) MS collection of notes and readings on statutes, 4 vols. [2001.6.5 Bonhams & Brooks], 4 (Box 40)
- Taussig Catalog # 311: 18th cent. (1720-29) MS reports in Court of Exchequer by Philip Ward, 2 vols. [2001.6.21(a) Bloomsbury Book Auctions], 2 (Box 41)
- Taussig Catalog # 312: 18th cent. (1705) MS statement of case of overseers of poor of Dullingham, 1 p. [2001.6.21(b) Bloomsbury Book Auctions] (Box 41)
- Taussig Catalog # 313: 18th cent. MS notebook listing cases 1702-25, 72 pp. [2001.6.21(c) Bloomsbury Book Auctions] (Box 41)
- Taussig Catalog # 313.1: 1800-1817 nine ALS from Charles Abbott to H. Bruce (Misc. 52) [2001.6.21(d) Bloomsbury Book Auctions] (Box 41)
- Taussig Catalog # 314.1-314.2: Littleton, Les tenures 1612 (printed), 2 vols., interleaved with extensive MS notes [2001.7.10 Sotheby's], 2 (Box 41)
- Taussig Catalog # 315: 18th cent. (9 Feb. 1832) case with autograph opinion of J.T. Coleridge [2001.9.22(a) Aitchison] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 316: Hale, Summary of the Pleas of the Crown 1694 (printed) interleaved and annotated [2001.10.3 Bonhams & Brooks] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 317: 17th cent. (c. 1695) MSS two cases concerning ships and Navigation Act 1660, [2001.11.17 Farrahar & Dupre] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 318: 17th cent. MSS two transcripts relating to the fall of Lord Keeper Williams, 9 + 6 pp. [2001.11.22(a) Bloomsbury Book Auctions] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 319: 17th cent. (c. 1621) MS tract by George Norbury on abuses of High Court of Chancery, 28 ff. [2001.11.22(b) Bloomsbury Book Auctions] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 320: 19th cent. (1818) MS summons to driver of overloaded stage-coach, 2 pp. [2001.11.12(a) Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 321: 18th cent. MS heads of a bill to rescue wrecked ships, 2 sh. [2001.12.12(b) Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 322: 19th cent. (1843) MS copy of case to and opinion of Barnes Peacock, 5 pp. + backsheet [2001.12.13(a) Aitchison] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 323: 19th cent. (1824) MS copy of case to and opinion of Thomas Pemberton, 2 sh. [2001.12.13(b) Aitchison] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 324: 19th cent. (c. 1823) MS copy of case to and opinion of Joshua Martin, 2 pp. [2001.12.13(c) Aitchison] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 325: 18th cent. MS reports of cases in Queen's Bench 1702-1706, perhaps attributable to Robert Raymond, 456 pp. [2002.3.6 Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 43 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 326: 18th cent. (1798-9) MS documents relating to Union Society of Carpenters [2002.4.18 Aitchison] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 327: 16th cent. MS precedents in Exchequer c. 1570-88, 74 ff. [2002.4.25(a) Swann Galleries, New York] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 328: 18th cent. MS reports of cases at Nisi Prius 1752-86, 186 ff. [2002.4.25(b) Swann Galleries, New York] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 329: 17th-18th cent. MS collection of court and conveyancing precedents c. 1670-1700 made by Philip Hawkins, c. 270 ff. [2002.5.17 R. Hatchwell] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 330: 18th cent. (1714) MS articles of clerkship with attorney, 1 sh. [2002.6.6 Francis Edwards] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 331: 19th cent. (1831-2) MS attorney's cash book, 130 pp. [2002.8.15(b) Aitchison] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 332: 19th cent. (1834-6) MS minute book of Select Vestry of Sunderland, 61 pp. [2002.8.28 Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 333: 17th cent. (20 July 1675) MS conveyance relating to settlement by Sir Matthew Hale, signed by him, s. sh. [2002.10.3(a) Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 334: 16th cent. (22 Dec. 1580) MS appointment by Sir Edmund Trafford sheriff of Lancashire of gaoler of Lancaster prison, 1 sh. [2002.10.3(c) Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 335: 19th cent (c.1801) MS customs of Knaresborough Forest - 30pp? [2002.10.3(d) Dominic Winter Book Auctions ]
- Taussig Catalog # 336: 18th cent. (1748) MS certificate re: cow disease, 1 p. [2003.3.17 James Cummins, New York] (Box 42)
- Taussig Catalog # 337: 18th cent. (1767) MS treasury warrant for transportation of convicts to America, 1 p. [2003.4.17 Mullock's Auctions] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 338: Bound collection of printed House of Lords cases 1786-88, with MS notes of judgments endorsed [2003.4.18 Bauman Rare Books] (Box 45 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 339.1-339.2: W. Grant, Law and lawyers 1840 (printed), with some MS material inserted, 2 vol. [2003.5.23 Keys Auctions, Aylsham], 2 (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 340: 18th cent. (2nd quarter) MS extracts from statutes relating to sewers and an account of the law relating to sewers, 67 pp. [2003.6.12 Bloomsbury Book Auctions] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 341: 18th cent MS copies of documents (including a long official letter and copy cases to and opinions of Dudley Ryder) relating to the requisitioning of grain by the Admiralty in 1743 (Misc. 27) [2003.6.27(a) Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 342: 19th cent. (1820) MSS, 2 depositions relating to rioting in Banbury in 1820, 4 pp. [2003.6.27(b) Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 343: 17th cent. (1606) MS evidence book (i.e., documents of title) of Salisbury House, 94 pp. [2003.7.22 Wildy] (Box 46 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 344: G. Jacob, Statute-law common-placed, 4th ed. 1739 (printed), interleaved and annotated [2003.8.21 Marrin & Sons] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 345: 18th cent. (1746) MS habeas corpus order to Keeper of Newgate gaol, 1 p. [2003.9.30(c) Aitchison] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 346: 18th cent. MS declaration of trust re: annuity society, 4 pp. [2003.9.30(d) Aitchison] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 347: 17th cent. MS collection of leaves from larger volume, precedents and miscellanea, 168 ff. [2003.11.11 Hatchwell] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 348: House of Lords cases 1774-91 (printed), with some annotations [2003.11.18 Dead Men's Minds] (Box 47 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 349: 1802 (12 Oct.) ALS from Richard Ford to Lord Pelham re policing in London, 8 pp. (Misc48) [2003.12.4(a) Mullock's Auctions] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 350: 1807 (15 Apr.) MS Autograph opinion of Nicolas C. Tindal, 2 pp. [2003.12.4(b) Mullock's] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 351: Lord Macmillan Law and other things 1937 (printed) with annotations by Mackinnon with three letters and one card from Macmillan to Mackinnon 1937-44 (Misc. 122) [2003.12.18 Alpha Books, California] (Box 44)
- Taussig Catalog # 352: 18th cent. MS copy of will dated 6 July 1697 of Sir Daniel Fleming and codicil dated 22 Mar. 1700, xi + ii ff. [2004.1.6 Fotheringham] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 353: 18th cent. MS collection of Scottish conveyancing and court precedents, 7-79 and 3-61 pp. [2004.2.5 Mullock's] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 354: 19th cent. (1759-62) MS Justice's notebook of Richard Tilden, 86 pp. [2004.3.18 Bloomsbury Book Auctions] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 355: 18th cent. MS collection, mainly precedents of pleading c. 1760-80, 142 pp. [2004.6.4 Fotheringham] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 356: 18th-19th cent MS large collection of precedents and copy cases to and opinions of counsel, 535 + 119 pp. [2004.6.25 Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 49 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 357: 18th cent. (c. 1762-95) collection of printed Revenue Acts with some MS annotations and indices [2004.9.20 Bookman (Norfolk)] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 358: 18th cent. (21 Feb. 1768) MS case to and autograph opinion of William Blackstone [2004.9.28(a) Bonhams] (Box 47 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 359: 11 May 1609 ALS of Sir Edward Coke to Archbishop Bancroft, 1 p. [2004.9.28(b) Bonhams] (Box 47 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 360: 8 Nov. 1594 ALS from Privy Council to sheriff and justices of Norfolk re: grain shortage, 2 pp. (Misc. 1) [2004.9.28(c) Bonhams] (Box 47 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 361: 18th cent. MS copy of case to and opinion of Edward Northey, 3 pp. [2004.12.9 Mullock's] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 362: 16th-17th cent. (c. 1600) MS treatise on law of sea-shore, 23 ff. [2005.2.2(a) Mullock's] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 363: 17th cent MS customs of manor of Corsham, 1689 - 30pp [2005.2.2(b) Mullock's]
- Taussig Catalog # 364: 18th cent. (1756) MS instrument of sale of reward for prosecution of felon, 2 pp. [2005.4.20(a) Mullock's] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 365: 18th cent. (1795) Prospectus of articles of tontine to fund repair of Hay bridge (printed), with MS letter [2005.4.20(b) Mullock's] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 366: 18th cent. (c. 1745) MS copies of proceedings in admiralty case from Newport, Rhode Island, 70 pp. [2005.6.16 Bloomsbury Book Auctions] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 367: 18th cent. (1706-10) British Merlin 1706 (printed) bound with MS notebook of Edward Benet, 18 + 82 ff. [2005.7.28 Aitchison] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 368: 18th cent. (1735) MS articles of clerkship in Chancery, 1 sh. [2005.8.31(a) Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 369: 17 Oct [1776] ALS from Lord Mansfield to unnamed peer, 1 p. (Misc. 33) [2005.8.31(b) Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 370: 28 Nov. 1720 ALS from William Lowndes to Sir Bibye Lake, 1 p. (Misc. 14) [2005.8.31(c) Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 371: 19th cent. MS copy of account of Monmouth rebellion and Abloody assizes, 4 pp. [2005.10.11(a) Aitchison] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 372: 19th cent. (18 July 1807) MS case to and autograph opinion of Sir Thomas Plumer, 3 pp. [2005.10.11(b) Aitchison] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 373: 19th cent. (1807) MS copy of case stated by Assessed Taxes Commissioners, 3 pp. [2005.10.28 Aitchison] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 374: 21 June 1816 ALS from Lord Ellenborough to Privy Council, 3 pp. (Misc. 63) [2005.11.10(a) J. Browning] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 375: 18 July 1754 ALS from Lord Hardwicke L.C. to unnamed correspondent, 2 pp. (Misc. 26) [2005.11.10(b) J. Browning] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 376.1: 18th cent. (1733-37) collection of printed House of Lords cases with MS notes of judgments endorsed on many [2005.11.14 Lawbook Exchange, New York] [1 of 2] (Box 50 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 376.2: 18th cent. (1733-37) collection of printed House of Lords cases with MS notes of judgments endorsed on many [2005.11.14 Lawbook Exchange, New York] [2 of 2] (Box 51 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 377: 18th cent. (25 May 1736) MS case to and opinion of Dudley Ryder, 2 sh. [2005.11.22 Farrahar & Dupre] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 378: 18th cent. undated ALS from Lord Mansfield to unnamed peer, 2 pp. (Misc. 31) [2005.11.29 Argosy Bookstore New York] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 379: 18th cent. MS notebook containing extracts from Blackstone and other matter, 68 pp. [2005.12.6 Aitchison] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 380: 18th cent. MS King's Bench reports (1736-7) compiled by Thomas Abney, 247 pp. [2006.1.15 Ebay] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 381: 18th cent. MS reports of actions on the case (1756-71), 127 ff. [2006.2.8 Brightwells Auctions] (Box 48)
- Taussig Catalog # 382: 17th cent. (last quarter) MS commonplace of Irish law student, 395 ff. [2006.2.15(1) Lawbook Exchange, New York] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 383: 18th cent. MS collection of materials relating mainly to Penry Williams sheriff of Breconshire, 13 items [2006.2.15(2) Mullock's] (Box 19 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 384: 17th cent. (1637) three MS letters to Privy Council from Yorkshire maltsters, each 1 p. [2006.2.15(3) Mullock's] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 385: 25 Jan. 1761 ALS from Col. Jonathan La Faussille to unnamed peer concerning riot by women spinners at Bradford-on-Avon with copy of reply, 4 pp. (Misc. 28.1) [2006.2.15(4) Mullock's] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 386: 11 Oct. 1769 ALS from Lord Conyngham to Joshua Sharp concerning appeals from Ireland, 2 pp. (Misc. 31.1) [2006.2.15(5) Mullock's] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 387: The Trader's Counsellor (c. 1824) (printed) interleaved and annotated [2006.3.7 Wildy] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 388: 17th cent. (c. 1634) two MS copies of speech by Lord Keeper Coventry to Sir John Finch, 4 pp. [2006.4.19 Mullock's] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 389: 17th-18th cent. (1697, 1704) MS accounts of King's Printer 1697, 1 + 3 + 2 pp. and Queen's Printer 1704, 1 p. [2006.4.29 A.R. Heath] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 390: 18th cent. (c. 1760) large MS volume containing copies of conveyances and opinions of counsel, 637 pp. [2006.6.15(a) Bloomsbury Auctions] (Box 53 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 391: 18th cent. (1st half) MS reports in King's Bench 1714-15, 338 pp. [2006.6.15(b) Bloomsbury Auctions] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 392: 17th cent. (c. 1605) undated ALS from Sir Edward Coke to Sir Nathaniel Bacon and Rice Gywnn re: woman alleged to have poisoned her husband, 1 sh. (Misc. 3.1) [2006.6.15(c) Sotheby's, New York] (Box 47 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 393: 18th cent. (c. 1638) MS record of argument of Sir John Bramston in ship-money case, 8 ff. [2006.6.21 Mullock's] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 394: 19th cent. (c. 1740) MS reports in King's Bench 1737-39, x + 407 + 238 pp. [2006.7.13(a) Sotheby's] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 395: 17th cent. MS entries, mainly from Interregnum to William & Mary, 336 + 11 pp. [2006.7.13(b) Sotheby's] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 396: 18th cent. (1774-75) MS trial notebook (criminal) of Sir John Burland, 233 ff. [2006.7.25(a) John Nicholson Auctioneers] (Box 52)
- Taussig Catalog # 397: 18th cent. (1774-6) MS trial notebook (nisi prius) of Sir John Burland, 232 ff. [2006.7.25(b) John Nicholson Auctioneers] (Box 54)
- Taussig Catalog # 398: 18th cent. (c. 1750) MS attorney's notebook, including some non-legal material, 10 + 79 + 238 pp. [2006.8.16 Brightwells Auctions] (Box 54)
- Taussig Catalog # 399: 18th cent. (c. 1750) MS Chancery commonplace, 279 pp. [2006.10.24 Lawbook Exchange, New York] (Box 54)
- Taussig Catalog # 400: R. Gardiner, Instructor clericalis, 7th ed., 1727 (printed), interleaved and annotated (c. 1730-40) [2007.2.7 Ebay] (Box 54)
- Taussig Catalog # 401: 18th cent. (mainly last quarter) MS group of papers from Thomas Adams of Alnwick [2007.2.15 Mullock's] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 402: 19th cent. Poor law amendment act (printed), with MS cases and opinions at end [2007.3.10 Ebay] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 403: 17th cent. (c. 1614) MS copy of bill in Chancery re: Dyer's debts, 14 sh. [2007.3.20 Aitchison] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 404: Field, An analysis of Blackstone's Commentaries, 2nd ed., 1817 (printed), interleaved and annotated [2007.4.12 Dominic Winter Book Auctions] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 405: 18th cent. (14 Dec. 1703) MS case to and autograph opinion of Nicholas Starkie, 2 pp. [2007.5.20 Aitchison] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 406: 19th cent. MS collection of copy cases and opinions, 348 pp. [2007.5.23 Thomson Roddick & Medcalf] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 407: 18th cent. four MS lists of books [2007.5.25 Wildy] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 408: 19th. cent (1832-38) MS account book of William Witham, stationer, 79 + 5 ff. [2007.6.14 G.C. Books (on ABE)] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 409: 18th-19th cent. small collection of ALS [2007.6.22 Mullock's] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 410: 18th cent. MS collection of copies of conveyancing and litigation drafts and cases to and opinions of counsel, 340 pp. [2007.8.7(a) C.R. Johnson] (Box 56 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 411: 18th cent. MS bill book of attorney, c. 1772-1796, 323 pp. [2007.8.7(b) Stride & Sons] (Box 57 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 412: 18th cent. (c. 1790) MS catalogue of law books, 4 pp. [2007.9.19 C.R. Johnson] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 413: 17th cent. (mainly 1640-60) MS memorandum book of Samuel Trotman, 150 (some missing) + 8 + 22 ff. [2007.10.2 C.R. Johnson] (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 414.1-414.4: 18th cent. MS account and note books of attorney [2007.11.7 Thomson Roddick & Medcalf] [1 of 2], 4 (Box 55)
- Taussig Catalog # 414.5-414.8: 18th cent. MS account and note books of attorney [2007.11.7 Thomson Roddick & Medcalf] [2 of 2], 4 (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 415: 17th-18th cent. large MS volume of copy conveyances [2007.12.8 Railton Auctions] (Box 59 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 416: 16th-18th cent. collection of MS materials relating to Middlesex Sessions (Hicks Hall) mounted in modern album [2007.12.19 C.R. Johnson] (Box 60 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 416 supp.: Supplement to no. 416 (Box 19 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 417: 3 Jan. 1980 ALS from Lord Hailsham to Richard Wilberforce [2008.1.26 Ebay] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 418: 17th cent. (1655) MS directions to prisoners on trial, 10 pp. [2008.3.12 Sotheby's] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 419: 19th cent. MS case to counsel (N. Lindley) [2008.4.14(a) Aitchison] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 420: MS legal notebook on printed militia forms [2008.4.14(b) Aitchison] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 421: 18th-19th cent. (c. 1775-1810) MS collection of conveyancing precedents, 270 pp. [2008.4.14(c) Aitchison] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 422: 18th cent. (1776) MS assignment of Northumberland gaol [2008.4.23 Thomson Roddick & Medcalf] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 423: 19th cent. (1812) MS letter from Home Department to Joseph Radcliffe re: Luddites, 4 pp. but lacking end of letter [2008.6.7 Ebay] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 424: 18th cent. (1740-48) twelve MS capias relating to Borough of Helsdon [2008.6.16 (a) Aitchison] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 425: 19th cent (1832) MS deed between Earl Spencer and others re dispute in Wimbledon - 1 sh. [2006.6.16 (b) Aitchison]
- Taussig Catalog # 426: 17th-19th cent. collection of unrelated MS material (including rental of Sir Edward Coke) in modern album [2008.7.22 Lawbook Exchange] (Box 61 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 427: 19th cent. (1827) group of letters re: passing off of coins [2008.8.8 Mullock's] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 428: ?19th cent. printed poor law form with information and directions relating to Sarah Jones [2008.8.18 Aitchison] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 429: 17th cent. MS arbitration award of Sir Robert Shaftoe [2008.9.25 Mullock's] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 430: 19th-20th cent. 2 MS fee books of Louis Diston Powles 1891-1903 [2008.10.14 Ebay] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 431: 18th cent. (3 March 1781) case to and opinion of William Wynne [2008.10.29 Aitchison] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 432: 8 Nov. 1799 ALS from T. Shelton to Robert Thorp written on printed order of Chancery dated 25 Apr. 1796 [2008.11.4 Fotheringham] (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 433: 18th cent. (1787-90) quantity of MS letters (c. 90) to Charles Wren from his London agents Kirton Grey and Walters [2008.11.6 Mullock's], 2 (Box 58)
- Taussig Catalog # 434: 17th-19th cent. large collection (c. 200) of MS cases to and opinions of counsel (some original and some copies) from Shrewsbury [2008.11.24 C.R. Johnson ex Bonhams 4 Nov. 2008] (Box 62)
- Taussig Catalog # 435: 17th cent. MS abridgement of cases c. 1650, c. 90 ff., badly damaged [2008.12.7 Ebay] (Box 63 (Oversize))
- Taussig Catalog # 436: Radcliffe The law and its compass(printed) with ALS from Radcliffe to John Sparrow [2008.12.17 Meyer Boswell Books] (Box 62)
- Taussig Catalog # 437: 19th cent. several groups of papers from Alnwick archive relating to shipwreck and the Duke of Northumberland [2009.1.31 K. Spelman], 4 (Box 62)
- Taussig Catalog # 438: 16th cent. (1540-95) MS Tudor precedent book, 48 ff. [2009.2.18(a) Meyer Boswell Books] (Box 62)
- Taussig Catalog # 439: 17th cent. MS reports of Charles I, 122 ff. [2009.2.18(b) Meyer Boswell Books] (Box 62)
- Taussig Catalog # 440: 17th cent. MS reports and memoranda of Roger Hill, 339 pp. [2009.2.18(c) Meyer Boswell Books] (Box 64)
- Taussig Catalog # 441.1-441.5: 17th-18th cent. (1689-1720) Vernon's MS reports and notebooks, 3 vols. reports, 2 vols. indexes, 5 vols. notebooks, vols. 1-5 [2009.2.18(d) Meyer Boswell Books], 5 (Box 64)
- Taussig Catalog # 441.6-441.11: 17th-18th cent. (1689-1720) Vernon's MS reports and notebooks, 3 vols. reports, 2 vols. indexes, 5 vols. notebooks, vols. 6-7 [2009.2.18(d) Meyer Boswell Books], 6 (Box 65)
- Taussig Catalog # 442: 18th cent. (1775-8) MS reports mainly King's Bench, 247 pp. [2009.2.18(e) Meyer Boswell Books] (Box 65)
- Taussig Catalog # 443: 19th cent. MS collection of copy cases to and opinions of counsel, 246 pp. [2009.2.18(f) Meyer Boswell Books] (Box 65)
- Taussig Catalog # 444: 19th cent. (3 Dec. 1805) case to and autograph opinion of John Hullock [2009.2.18(g) Meyer Boswell Books] (Box 65)
- Taussig Catalog # 445.1-445.2: T. Vernon, Cases argued and adjudged in the High Court of Chancery 1726 and 1728, 2 vols. (printed), annotated by Sir Thomas Clarke [2009.3.4 Meyer Boswell Books], 2 (Box 65)
- Taussig Catalog # 446: 19th cent. (c. 1831) collection of c. 100 letters to Robert Thorp [2009.3.5(a) Mullock's], 7 (Box 66)
- Taussig Catalog # 447: 18th & 19th cent. MS notebook and other papers from Alnwick archive [2009.3.5(b) Mullock's], 2 (Box 66)
- Taussig Catalog # 448: 18th cent. (c. 1760-67) part of MS legal commplace, 121 ff. [2009.5.14(a) Bloomsbury Auctions] (Box 66)
- Taussig Catalog # 449: 18th cent. MS notebook of of reports 5-18 George II, 178 pp. [2009.5.14(b) Bloomsbury Auctions] (Box 66)
- Taussig Catalog # 450: Precedents in Chancery...1689 to 1722(printed), with MS annotations by Sir Thomas Clarke [2009.5.15 Meyer Boswell Books] (Box 66)
- Taussig Catalog # 451.1-451.2: 18th cent. (c. 1711-80) collection of MS clerkship deeds and documents relating to Thomas Adams and his clerks [2009.6.11(a) Thomson Roddick & Medcalf] [1 of 2], 2 (Box 66)
- Taussig Catalog # 451.3: 18th cent. (c. 1711-80) collection of MS clerkship deeds and documents relating to Thomas Adams and his clerks [2009.6.11(a) Thomson Roddick & Medcalf] [2 of 2] (Box 67)
- Taussig Catalog # 452: 18th cent. (c. 1780-1790) collection of letters from Alnwick archive from variety of sources (including Leneney & Sayers and Elizabeth Cookson) to Wren & Airey and others [2009.6.11(b) Thomson Roddick & Medcalf], 4 (Box 67)
- Taussig Catalog # 453: 18th cent. (c. 1790) various MS papers relating to office of Clerk of Peace, Northumberland [2009.6.25(a) Mullock's], 2 (Box 67)
- Taussig Catalog # 454: 18th cent. (1750-65) MS letters to Thomas Adams [2009.6.25(b) Mullock's] (Box 67)
- Taussig Catalog # 455.1-455.5: 18th-19th cent. large collection from Alnwick archive including bills from Thomas Adams to his clients and correspondence with Charles Wren [2009.6.25(c) Mullock's] [1 of 2], 5 (Box 67)
- Taussig Catalog # 455.6-455.7: 18th-19th cent. large collection from Alnwick archive including bills from Thomas Adams to his clients and correspondence with Charles Wren [2009.6.25(c) Mullock's] [2 of 2], 2 (Box 67)
- Taussig Catalog # 456: 18th cent. MS notebook of Robert Thorp entitled A1799 Newcastle business [2009.7.16 Thomson Roddick & Medcalf] (Box 68)